HUNTER JOHNSON

SUMMARY

Full Stack Software Developer particularly interested in scalability, security, and performance. Obsessed with providing clean, well-documented code. Over 4 years' experience at global defense, marketing firms, and other digital agencies. Open source author and maintainer of various Javascript packages with a focus on theming Linux environments and tooling securely.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Lockheed Martin UCF CWEP

Full Stack Web Developer

July 2018 - present

One of the core developers responsible for developing and maintaining web applications that support the production operations team.

Work on a wide range of tasks that encompass the entire development flow, including web development (Javascript, PHP, Oracle), user experience, and user interface design.

Responsible for the highly regarded navigation system which is used across all applications.

Fixed a variety of bugs and annoyances that had been present for years.

Implemented multiple applications that save thousands in revenue yearly and support the green initiative.

9seven Design

Full Stack Web Developer

January 2016 - June 2018

Developed user-centric, performant websites for high revenue clients.

Implemented refined back-end dashboard that was by far the most requested feature.

Designed unique user interactions using Figma.

Responsible for application server setup, maintenance, and security.

PROJECTS

Preme-o

Desktop application (Electron, React, Redux, Node.js) that allows users to purchase limited stock items from supremenewyork.com.

Developed UI that follows ally guidelines, being regarded as one of the most user-friendly bots. Integrated secure way to authenticate user licenses using JWT web token validation and Auth0.

Captcha Harvester

Implemented a clever way to harvest Google ReCaptcha tokens from websites such as supremenewyork and palaceskateboards.

Integrated feature to support any site that uses ReCaptcha.

Gotham Sublime Text 3 UI Theme

Dark Sublime Text 3 UI theme ported to match the Gotham color scheme.

Accepted into Package Control with 4k installs and counting.

JWT Validation API

Developed JWT validation API (Golang) to facilitate the validation of requests through preme-o. Migrated the API to use serverless functions via the Zeit platform, saving money while at the same time scaling better.

EDUCATION

University of Central Florida, Orlando, Florida

B.S. Major in Information Technology

May 2016 – present

GPA: 3.3

SKILLS / KEYWORDS

Linux: Arch Linux, Debian family (Ubuntu, Debian) Scripting: Bash and utils (sed, awk, grep), Python

Backend: Node.js, Golang, Java, PHP

Frontend: Javascript, React, AngularJS, HTML, CSS

Databases: Oracle, PostgreSQL, Redis

Web Application servers/proxies: Nginx, Apache

Misc: Redux, Git, AWS, Zeit, JWT, C